// This is the data for the quiz questions, answers, and choices
var quizData = [
  {
    "question": "What definition of pop culture argues that popular culture is considered inferior because of its accessibility. ",
    "answer": "Popular culture is whatever is left after you have identified what ❝high culture❞ is.",
    "choices": [
      "Popular culture is whatever is left after you have identified what ❝high culture❞ is.",
      "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored (or well- liked) by many people."
    ],
    "reference": "First Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What definition of pop culture states that popular culture is authentic (created by the people) instead of commercial (thrust upon them by commercial enterprises).",
    "answer": "Popular culture is folk culture, something that arises from the people rather than imposed upon them. ",
    "choices": [
      "Popular culture can be defined as commercial objects that are produced for mass consumption by non-discriminating consumers.",
      "Popular culture is folk culture, something that arises from the people rather than imposed upon them. "
    ],
    "reference": "First Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What definition of pop culture states users are free to embrace some manufactured content, alter it for their own use, or reject it entirely and create their own. ",
    "answer": "In the postmodern world (i.e., today), the distinction between ❝authentic❞ versus ❝commercial❞ is blurred",
    "choices": [
      "In the postmodern world (i.e., today), the distinction between ❝authentic❞ versus ❝commercial❞ is blurred",
      "Popular culture is negotiated. "
    ],
    "reference": "First Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What category of pop culture encompasses anything and everything politics-related, which includes politicians and political events?",
    "answer": "Politics",
    "choices": [
      "Politics",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "reference": "First Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What encompasses varied forms of media, but it usually includes television, film, music, and literature; also covers celebrities and artists?",
    "answer": "Entertainment",
    "choices": [
      "Entertainment",
      "Sports"
    ],
    "reference": "First Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three popular culture milestones that existed among ancient societies?",
    "answer": "wedding ceremonies, music, and fashion",
    "choices": [
      "death ceremonies, music, and fashion",
      "wedding ceremonies, music, and fashion"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What era did Western composers began to commit their music into paper and share it to other musicians?",
    "answer": "Renaissance",
    "choices": [
      "Baroque",
      "Renaissance"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What culture stems from the ideas and tendencies of the working class to sort out the ones that shall be kept for their importance and consumer value?",
    "answer": "Pop Culture",
    "choices": [
      "Pop Culture",
      "Folk Culture"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What fashion trend was happening around the Medieval period in the West?",
    "answer": "Aristocrats and the royalty began to wear clothes that took these pieces of clothing beyond functionality; the working class began to emulate these outfits.",
    "choices": [
      "Aristocrats and the royalty began to wear clothes that took these pieces of clothing beyond functionality; the working class began to emulate these outfits.",
      "Fashion was determined by cultural caste.\r\r\n"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the English playwright whose works bridged both fine art and popular art, making his works appeal to many?",
    "answer": "William Shakespeare",
    "choices": [
      "William Shakespeare",
      "John Ronald Reuel Tolkien"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What period in history did globalization start to occur?",
    "answer": "The Age of Exploration",
    "choices": [
      "The Post-Modern Age",
      "The Age of Exploration"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What illegal drug almost ruined China because the British voyagers introduced it to their black market?",
    "answer": "Opium",
    "choices": [
      "Opium",
      "Marijuana"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What substance, previously used in Mesoamerican rituals, became an instant hit to the European market due to the upcoming slave trade boom?",
    "answer": "chocolate",
    "choices": [
      "chocolate",
      "vanilla"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What canal was completed that allowed the Philippines the access  to the popular cultures of the West, which included novels, knowledge, and music, among other things back in the 1860s?",
    "answer": "Suez Canal",
    "choices": [
      "Grand Canal",
      "Suez Canal"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a solemn rite dedicated for two (2) humans to form a pact between them to love each other and make their lives work as one -- usually under the providence of their preferred deity?",
    "answer": "Wedding",
    "choices": [
      "Wedding",
      "Bar Mitzvah"
    ],
    "reference": "Second Quiz",
    "term": "PRELIMS"
  }
]